

# Jerry Lott

Laurel, MS 39440 (601) 778-5060 mycareers@jerrylott.com

# WEBSITE, ( PORTFOLIO, **PROFILES**

Personal Website: https://jerrylott.com/ GitHub: https://github.com/lottjerry

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jerrylott/

# PROFESSIONAL () SUMMARY

Very motivated and fast learning Freelance Web Developer brings enthusiasm and detailed understanding of various programming languages to webpage planning, development and maintenance. Experience designing and developing sites from concept to roll out. Foundational grasp of various CSS and HTML options, development platforms and security requirements.

#### SKILLS

- Proficient in Mathematics. Mainly
- Calculus and Linear
- Programming/Algebra.
- Moderate experience in
- Microsoft
- Office.
- Experience using GitHub (Web
- And Desktop) and Git
- Some experience in Cyber
- Security.
- Quick and Adaptive Learner.
- Excellent teamwork and leadership
- Skills.
- Worked in fast-paced environment.

- Demonstrates excellent job
- Performance in productivity,
- Quality, safety, and attendance.
- Excellent communication skills.
- Tech savvv.
- Fast and accurate typist
- PC and Laptop wipe/restore and
- Repair.
- Graphic Design skills.
- Moderate experience in many
- Programming languages: Python and C++ (Mainly Python)
- Moderate experience in Front-End
- HTML 5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, Bootstrap

#### WORK HISTORY

#### **ASSISTANT MANAGER**

01/2018 to CURRENT

### Corner Market | Ellisville, MS

- Assisted customers with locating and choosing merchandise in any store department
- Assessed sales reports to identify and enhance sales performance, support inventory oversight, and capitalize on emerging trends
- Implemented daily operating procedures to keep store clean, adequately stocked, and well-organized
- Coached employees and trained on methods for handling various aspects of sales, complicated issues, and difficult customers

- Walked through department multiple times each shift to evaluate and correct issues such as cleaning, and stock replenishment needs
- Exceeded sales goals and accomplished business objectives by inspiring staff and promoting target products
- Offered hands-on assistance to customers, assessing needs, and maintaining current knowledge of consumer preferences
- Assisted customers by answering questions and fulfilling requests
- Maintained clean, adequately stocked, and organized store by streamlining daily operations and introducing new procedures
- Greeted customers and helped with product questions, selections, and purchases including in-store and e-service transactions
- Assigned jobs to individual employees by considering factors such as previous training, current abilities, and general knowledge
- Trained employees in stock
- Order stock using a handheld scanner
- Open store which included counting money in the safe for accuracy and correcting employees time from the previous day.

#### **MERCHANDISER**

09/2015 to 10/2017

# Coca Cola Bottling Co Consolidated | Laurel, MS

- Merchandised new stock to appeal to customers, grab attention and drive sales
- Monitored inventory levels and kept adequate stock in product displays on sales floor
- Partnered with sales representatives and managers to coordinate delivery and merchandising schedule
- Worked with managers and advertising directors to optimize promotions
- Unloaded arriving product stock and moved to store display areas
- Answered customer questions regarding store merchandise, department information and pricing
- Removed damaged, out-of-code, not-in-set and discontinued items from displays
- Rotated manufacturer products as needed
- Loaded and unloaded merchandise using ladder and pallet jack
- Verified products appeared at correct locations in proper quantities
- Inspected merchandise for quality and arranged proper display location on floor
- Established strong vendor relationships to maintain and support business.

## PRODUCTION ASSOCIATE

02/2015 to 08/2015

## Canadian Harvest | Louisville, KY

- Packaging
- Shrink Wrapping
- Sanitizing

FC 11/2013 to 01/2015

## ASSOCIATE, Amazon SDF | Jeffersonville, IN

Evaluated merchandise for irregularities, flaws, or damage prior to packing

- Selected packing materials based on size, quantity, and fragility of package contents
- Maintained compliance with company safety policies and called violations to attention of management
- Transported merchandise to sales floor and replenished out-of-stock and low-stock items
- Alternated goods in inventory by observing first-in/first-out approach to keep shelves organized and properly stocked
- Reviewed order slips picked products and staged merchandize to be shipped
- Promoted warehouse safety by reporting or resolving safety hazards and observing OSHA guidelines.

#### **EDUCATION** $\Diamond$

**Bachelor of Science** | Computer Science, Mathematics

05/2021

University of Southern Mississippi, Hattiesburg, MS

Associate of Science | Computer and Information Systems Technology 08/2011

Jones County Junior College, Ellisville, MS

**High School Diploma** 

05/2009

Northeast Jones High School, Laurel, MS

#### REFERENCES (

#### Haylie Pierotti

Address: 2800 Lincoln Rd, Hattiesburg, MS 39402

Work: (601) 325-9164 Cell: (601) 935-0532

Email: hayliejpierotti@yahoo.com Relation: Assistant Manager/Friend

#### · Dr. Beddhu Murali

Address: Chain Technology Center, Hattiesburg, MS 39406, Office: 210

Work: (601) 266-4949

Email: Beddhu.Murali@usm.edu

Relation: Professor

#### · Dr. Dia Ali

Address: Chain Technology Center, Hattiesburg, MS 39406, Office: 209

Work: (601) 266-4949

Email: Beddhu.Murali@usm.edu

Relation: Professor

# - Jennifer Powell

Address: J.B. Young Main - 204 900 South Court Street Ellisville, Ms 39437

Work: (601) 477-4064

Email: jennifer.powell@jcjc.edu

Relation: Professor